[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the film The Break-Up, when do Gary and Brooke\u2019s friends conclude their relationship is over?", "correct_answer": "At the games night", "incorrect_answers": ["At the couple bowling night", "At the baseball game", "At an art gallery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor is a graduate of Harvard University and of the Yale Drama School. In 1997 he married Angela Bassett. He is known for his role as A.D.A. Ron Carver on Law and Order: Criminal Intent.", "correct_answer": "Courtney Vance", "incorrect_answers": ["Vincent DOnofrio", "Chris Noth", "Eric Bogodsian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Opel first showed cars of their own design in 1902 at this motor show in Germany.", "correct_answer": "Hamburg Motor Show", "incorrect_answers": ["Internationale Automobil-Ausstellung, Frankfurt", "Hanover Motor Show", "Auto Mobil International, Leipzig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who created the James Bond character?", "correct_answer": "Ian Fleming", "incorrect_answers": ["Alistair MacLean", "James Herriot", "Leslie Charteris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In cinematography, a close-up of an object or detail within a scene is referred to as what?", "correct_answer": "Insert shot", "incorrect_answers": ["Cutaway", "Reveal", "Cue shot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This answering machine message is from what movie: If you utter so much as one syllable, Ill hunt you down and gut you like a fish. If youd like to fax me, press the star key.?", "correct_answer": "How the Grinch Stole Christmas", "incorrect_answers": ["Shaun of the Dead", "Meet the Fockers", "The Bourne Supremacy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the Papstiche Schweizergarde?", "correct_answer": "A 500 year-old organization of Swiss guards", "incorrect_answers": ["The formal name for the Alps", "A 500 year-old brewery in Basel, Switzerland", "A garden in Switzerland dedicated to peace"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the planes destination in the film Snakes on a Plane?", "correct_answer": "Los Angeles", "incorrect_answers": ["Bali", "New York", "Hawaii"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Not all rain reaches the Earths surface.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the occupation of Tom Cruises character Cole Trickle in the 1990 movie Days of Thunder?", "correct_answer": "Auto racer", "incorrect_answers": ["American football player", "Sports journalist", "Automobile mechanic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A printer is an input device used to scan photos, pictures, texts and other printed material.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie does Father Barry get crushed by a falling crate, after preaching to his flock of stevedores to oppose local crime boss Johnnie Friendly.", "correct_answer": "On the Waterfront", "incorrect_answers": ["Marty", "A Streetcar Named Desire", "One-Eyed Jacks"]}]